Guide to the Class of 1958, Yale College, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- "58 Men" feature documentary on the Yale Class of 1958 [Video recordings], 1992, 2009; Accession 2018-A-037
  - Original camera masters of interviews
    - #105 master-Nick Kindred part II, Donald Caton, Ken Newburger, Ronald Burch, Goodyear, Newberger, Rathbone, Tatterfield, Undated (Box 6)
    - #106 master-Newberger, Rathbone, Tatterfield Part II, Callaway, Duff, McMurray, Sellers, Damon Wells and David Underwood, Alex Mourelatos and Thomas Seung Part I, Undated (Box 7)
    - #107 master-Mourelatos and Seung Part II, 1993 June 27 (Box 8)
    - #108 master-Jim Beckman and Terry Ryan, Neil and Dorothy Kaminsky, Chris Carroll and Don Uhlmann Part I, 1992 June 29 (Box 9)
    - #109 master-Chris Carroll and Don Uhlmann Part II, Uhlmann family party and Uhlmann in pool, 1992 July 4 (Box 10)
    - #110 master-Linden Blue, 1992 July 5 (Box 11)
    - #111 master-Jim M. and John Norton, Bob O'Mara and John Morton, Diane F., Fred Bode, David Adnopoz, 1992 July 7 (Box 12)
    - #112 master-Rich Alexander, Spike Bragg, Scott Gunn, Mike Schoettle and Jack Bogan, 1992 July 8 (Box 13)
    - #113 master-Brandon Stoddard, David Adnopoz (late), Lee Ault, Bill Fitzgerald, Tom Sargent (left early) and Ronald M. Sohigian, 1992 July 9 (Box 14)
    - #114 master-Joe Chinn, Peter Taft and family, Gordon Green and Gil Saliba and wives, Richard Gilinsky and Ernie Scheyhing and families, 1992 July 10 (Box 15)
    - #115 master-Big Sur test with Bergman, Jack Bogan Part II, and Frank Stockdale, 1992 July 13 (Box 16)
    - #116 master-San Francisco party, 1992 July 14 (Box 17)
    - #117 master-Georges St. Laurent and Maury Holland, 1992 July 20 (Box 18)
    - #118 master, 1992 July 24 (Box 19)
    - #119 master-Allen Sinell, Rory and Demi Cross (tape damaged near 1:26), 1992 July 25 (Box 20)
    - #120 master-Aerial shots Livingston to Jackson, John Pendexter, and Barker Hickox, 1992 July 29 (Box 21)
    - #121 master-Tim Foote (project manager) and Jonathan Foote (bad tape near hour one), 1992 July 29 (Box 22)
    - #122 master-Jonathan Foote Part II (promotional), 1992 July 29 (Box 23)
    - #123 master-Steve Silberstein, Peter Pool Davis, CA and Reno, NV, 1992 July 17 (Box 24)
    - #124 master, 1992 August 1 (Box 25)
    - #125 master-Bill Earley, Undated (Box 26)
    - #126 master, 1992 August 6 (Box 27)
    - #127 master-Bob and Ruth Carlson, Arthur Lubke, Peter and Jill Theis, 1992 August 10 (Box 28)
    - #128 master, 1992 August 12 (Box 29)
    - #129 master-John Esserman hot air balloonist, 1992 August 16 (Box 30)
    - #130 master-Bob Covington, Nashville, 1992 August 19 (Box 31)
    - #131 master-Sam McCalmont and Bob Beiring, 1992 August 21 (Box 32)
    - #132 master-Dick Manoogian, Detroit, 1992 August 24 (Box 33)
    - #133 master-John Preston, Detroit, Bob and Barb Holland, Columbus, 1992 August 25 (Box 34)
    - #134 master-South Bass Island, 1992 August 27 (Box 35)
    - #135 master-Lanny Baird's party, Rusnak, McCartney, Beatty, Bartlett, Burt and John Crossman, Undated (Box 36)
    - #136 master-Harold Williamson and Jack Genskow, Undated (Box 37)
    - #137 master-John Lee, 1992 September 8 (Box 38)
    - #138 new master, 1993 April 28 (Box 39)
    - #139 new master, 1993 April 28 (Box 40)
    - #140 master, Undated (Box 41)
    - #141 master-Linus Travers, Undated (Box 42)
    - #142 master, Undated (Box 43)
    - #143 master-carriaging in Delaware, Undated (Box 44)
    - #144 master-David Erlich, 1992 September 26 (Box 45)
    - #145 master-Baltimore Orioles game, Camden Yard, 1992 September 27 (Box 46)
    - #146 master, 1992 September 29 (Box 47)
    - #147 master, 1992 September 30 (Box 48)
    - #148 master, Undated (Box 49)
    - #149 master, Undated (Box 50)
    - #150 master, Undated (Box 51)
    - #151 master, Undated (Box 52)
    - #152 master, Undated (Box 53)
    - #153 master-Dr. Robert Ascheim, 1992 October 7 (Box 54)
    - #154 master, 1992 October 11 (Box 55)
    - #155 master-Harold Janeway, 1992 October 15 (Box 56)
    - #156 master-Kennedy-Duchin, music for credits, 1992 October 10 (Box 57)
    - #157 master-Peter Duchin Part II, Dan Robinson and Tom Wheeler, 1992 October (Box 58)
    - #158 master-Robert McDonald 1-30 NYC and Roger and Maria Lee, Paris, 1992 October (Box 59)
    - #159 master, 1992 October 21 (Box 60)
    - #160 master, 1992 October 22 (Box 61)
    - #161 master-Washington, D.C., 1992 October 24 (Box 62)
    - #162 master-Sullivan and John Riggs, Paris, 1992 October 26 (Box 63)
    - #163 master-Basil Carmody and Henry Pilsbury, Paris, 1992 October 27 (Box 64)
    - #164 master, 1992 November 1 (Box 65)
    - #165 master-Bush rally at Millpond Tavern, 1992 November 1 (Box 66)
    - #166 master-Larry Bensky interview at Pacifica News, 1992 November 4 (Box 67)
    - #167 master, 1992 November 5 (Box 68)
    - #168 master-Yale Club, 1992 November 5 (Box 69)
    - #169 master-John Turner and Victor Kovner, Sherman and Peg Bull, 1992 November 5 (Box 70)
    - #170 master-Jim Hoge, Council on Foreign Relations, 1992 November 6 (Box 71)
    - #171 master-New Haven Lawn Club and Jeff Sammons, 1992 November 12 (Box 72)
    - #172 master, 1992 November 12 (Box 73)
    - #173 master-Maine, Karl Crawford, and Yale vs. Princeton game, 1992 November 15 (Box 74)
    - #174 master, 1992 November 14 (Box 75)
    - #175 master-Joel with Banjo at office with girls, Doug Daniels et al in crazy outfit-New Haven, Julian Begien after Harvard game, Cambridge, Undated (Box 76)
    - #176 master-Harry Harlow, Drew Brooke (74) and Trevor (79), 1992 November 21 (Box 77)
    - #177 master-Bob Stubbs Cambridge, MA, 1992 November 21 (Box 78)
    - #178 master-David Sauer, 1992 November 22 (Box 79)
    - #179 master-Dick Cavett, 1992 November 24 (Box 80)
    - #180 master-3 sets of twins, 1993 January 16 (Box 81)
    - #181 master-Jack Embersits, 1993 January 27 (Box 82)
    - #182 master-Behind the scenes "The Dick Cavett Show" with Liv Uhlman and Peter Duchin interview, 1993 January 19 (Box 83)
    - #183 master-New Haven Lawn Club and Peter Duchin orchestra, 1993 January 19 (Box 84)
  - Digital Betacam master, 2009 April 17 (Box 85)
  - "58 Men" copies
    - VHS, 2009 April 17 (Box 86)
    - DVD, 2009 April 17 (Box 87)
  - Production files
    - "The Humbling of the Harvard Man" news clippings, 1994 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Interview transcripts, 1993 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - "58 Men" scripts, 1993 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Yale College Class of 1958 25th reunion book, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - C.D.B. Bryan notes, Undated (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Cavett interview transcripts, 1993 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Re-transfer: records of tapes, Undated (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Flyers, 1993 (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Interview lists, 1993 (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Photographs of classmates, 1992 (Box 88, Folder 10-12)